1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Publications 6347 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- News Clippings, 1997-2012 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Item 2: On he anniversary of Martin Luther King Jr.'s death, a call to make joining a union a civil right, 2012; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Notes: April 3, 2012.
  - Item 3: Summary of EFCA, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Employee Free Choice Act Toolkit
  - Item 4: A Parade With a Purpose, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Daniel Wallace; Claudia Vargas
    Notes: September 4, 2007.
  - Item 5: The Right to Organize, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: New York Times
    Notes: Editorial. March 6, 2007.
  - Item 6: Rallying call for labor cites union power in election, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: James Bertolone
    Notes: September 22, 2006.
  - Item 7: Clarissa St. Honors Past, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Michael Ziegler
    Notes: August 20, 2006.
  - Item 8: Financial abuses outlined at hearing, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Jonathan Epstein
    Notes: September 21, 2006.
  - Item 9: The 9,000 Word Mitchell Kaidy Reader, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Mitchell Kaidy
  - Item 10: Union Leader Rivera a potent Medicaid ally, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Jay Gallagher
    Notes: March 29, 2004.
  - Item 11: Episcopal home Oks settlement over union, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Michael Wentzel
    Notes: December 20, 2003.
  - Item 12: No union at ECH, yet, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Christine Carrie Fien
    Notes: v.33:no.15 (2003/2004:December 30/January 6)
  - Item 13: Our Whole Community Loses When Workers' Rights are Violated, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Bruce Popper; James Bertolone
    Notes: January 9, 2004.
  - Item 14: U.N. Declaration envisions more quality of life, freedom, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Notes: January 23, 2004.
  - Item 15: 2 Nursing Homes in Greece Unionize, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Joy Davia
    Notes: May 14, 2004.
  - Item 16: 100 urge Jordan center rescue, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Matt Leingang
    Notes: April 24, 2002.
  - Item 17: Pataki Details a Shift to Managed Care, and Exemptions, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Raymond Hernandez
    Notes: July 16, 1997.
  - Item 18: The Odd Couple That Did the Heavy Lifting on Pataki's Managed-Care Medicaid Deal, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Steven Greenhouse
  - Item 19: Politics plays key role in parade., 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Jack Jones
    Notes: September 7, 2004.
  - Item 20: Better growth for unions may rely on card signings, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Notes: September 4, 2004.
  - Item 21: 1199SEIU Members March in Rochester Labor Day Parade, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Notes: September 12, 2006.
  - Item 22: Unions Holding Their Own, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Patrick Flanigan
    Notes: September 2, 2007.
  - Item 23: New law makes assault on nurses a felony, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Deborah A. Miles
    Notes: December 2010-January 2011
  - Item 24: The Organization Man, 2009; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Daniel Massey
    Notes: July 28, 2009.
  - Item 25: Online Updates: 1199ers March in Rochester Puerto Rican Day Parade, 2009; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Notes: August 3, 2009. e-mail newsletter
  - Item 26: You promised me a raise, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Notes: cartoon
  - Item 27: Rotten Apples, Core Values, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Ari Paul
    Notes: August30/September 6, 2010.
  - Item 28: Labor Day Remarks of Bruce Popper, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Labor News
    Notes: v.65:no.18 (2010:September 17)
  - Item 29: Remarks of Bruce Popper, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Bruce Popper
    Notes: September 6, 2010.
  - Item 30: One Nation Working Together, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: One Nation
  - Item 31: One Nation Working Together, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Item 32: The Tea Party hasn't won yet, and it doesn't have the truth on its side, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Notes: September 24, 2010.
  - Item 33: War On Public Workers, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Amy Traub
    Notes: July 1, 2010.
  - Item 34: The State of the Unions, 2008; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Notes: Chapter 13 from The Big Squeeze
  - Item 35: Demystifying Unemployment Insurance, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Bond, Schoeneck and King
    Notes: Printout of PowerPoint presentation
  - Item 36: A Vision for Rochester, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: William Cala
    Notes: Remarks of Dr. William Cala at the Metro Justice Annual Dinner, May 2, 2010.
  - Item 37: "All Labor Has Dignity", 2011; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Martin Luther King, Jr.; Michael K. Honey
    Notes: Introductin only
  - Item 38: March With Us: We Are One, Respect Our Rights, 2011; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Notes: April 4, 2011.
  - Item 39: Fight for Economic Justice, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Metro Justice
  - Item 40: Bob Master Presentation at the WNYALF Annual Meeting, 2011; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Bob Master
    Notes: March 26, 2011.
- Text of AFL-CIO Membership Report for 2004, Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Text of AFL-CIO Membership Report for 2004, Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Health Care Reform and the Affordable Care Act, Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Health Care Reform and the Affordable Care Act, Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Author: HealthCare.gov
- No Holds Barred, 2009; Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: No Holds Barre: The Intensification of Employer Opposition to Organizing, 2009; Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
    Author: Kate Bronfenbrenner
    Notes: EPI Briefing Paper, May 20, 2009.
- Union Contract Ratification Vote 2007, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Union Contract Ratification Vote, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    Notes: October 10, 2007.
- What Happened to Our Standard of Living?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: What Happened To Our Standard of Living?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
- ILR Press 1997, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: ILR Press, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    Author: NYSSILR
- Uniting for a Better Future, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Uniting for a Better Future for Our Patients and Our Profession, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Author: 1199SEIU Nurse Alliance
  - Item 2: Uniting for a Better Future for Our Patients and Our Profession, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Unite to Win, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Unite To Win, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Author: Unite To Win
  - Item 2: Unite To Win, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Porque Razon Las Uniones?, 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
  Spanish
  - Item 1: Porque Razon Las Uniones?, 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Author: AFL- CIO
    Language: Spanish.
- Rochester Labor Film Series 2012, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: 23rd Annual Rochester Labor Film Series, 2012; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Author: Rochester Labor Council
- A New Face for American Labor 1992, Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: A New Face for American Labor, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    Author: Sam Roberts
    Notes: Reprint from New York Times Magazine, May 10, 1992.
- Respect 2003, Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Respect, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Notes: Summer 2003.
- Shock Waves, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Shock Waves, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    Notes: Reprint from Healthcare Worker Update, v.8:no.4 (1994:Fall/Winter)
- 1199 News 1999, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 1199 News, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: 1199
    Notes: v.15:no.1-2 (1997:January/February)
  - Item 2: 1199 News, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.17:no.1 (1999:January/February)
  - Item 3: 1199 News, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.17:no.3 (1999:April)
  - Item 4: 1199 News, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.17:no.4 (1999:May)
- 1199 SEIU News 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: 1199SEIU News, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.3 (2002:April)
    Language: English;Chinese.
  - Item 2: 1199SEIU News, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.4 (2002:May)
  - Item 3: 1199SEIU News, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.5 (2002:June)
  - Item 4: 1199SEIU News, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.8 (2002:October)
  - Item 5: 1199SEIU News, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.9 (2002:November)
  - Item 6: 1199SEIU News, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.1 (2003:January/February)
  - Item 7: 1199SEIU News, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.5 (2003:June)
  - Item 8: 1199SEIU News, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.6 (2003:July/August)
- America @ Work 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: America @ Work, 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Author: AFL-CIO Public Affairs Department
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1996:October)
  - Item 2: America @ Work, 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1996:November/December)
  - Item 3: America @ Work, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1997:January)
  - Item 4: America @ Work, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1997:February)
  - Item 5: America @ Work, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1997:March)
  - Item 6: America @ Work, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1997:April)
  - Item 7: America @ Work, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.5 (1997:May/June)
  - Item 8: America @ Work, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1997:July)
  - Item 9: America @ Work, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.7 (1997:August)
  - Item 10: America @ Work, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.8 (1997:September)
  - Item 11: America @ Work, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.9 (1997:October)
  - Item 12: America @ Work, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.10 (1997:November)
  - Item 13: America @ Work, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.11 (1997/1998:December/January)
  - Item 14: America @ Work, 1998; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1998:February)
  - Item 15: America @ Work, 1998; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1998:March)
  - Item 16: America @ Work, 1998; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (1998:April)
  - Item 17: America @ Work, 1998; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.4 (1998:May)
  - Item 18: America @ Work, 1998; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.5 (1998:June)
  - Item 19: America @ Work, 1998; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.6 (1998:July)
  - Item 20: America @ Work, 1998; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.7 (1998:August)
  - Item 21: America @ Work, 1998; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.8 (1998:September)
  - Item 22: America @ Work, 1998; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.9 (1998:October)
- America @ Work 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: America @ Work, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1999:January)
  - Item 2: America @ Work, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (1999:February)
  - Item 3: America @ Work, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (1999:March)
  - Item 4: America @ Work, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1999:April)
  - Item 5: America @ Work, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (1999:May)
  - Item 6: America @ Work, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.4:no.6 (1999:June)
  - Item 7: America @ Work, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.4:no.7 (1999:July)
  - Item 8: America @ Work, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.4:no.8 (1999:August)
  - Item 9: America @ Work, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.4:no.9 (1999:September)
  - Item 10: America @ Work, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.4:no.10 (1999:October)
  - Item 11: America @ Work, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.4:no.11 (1999:November/December)
  - Item 12: America @ Work, 2000; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (2000:January)
  - Item 13: America @ Work, 2000; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (2000:February)
  - Item 14: America @ Work, 2000; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (2000:March)
  - Item 15: America @ Work, 2000; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (2000:April)
  - Item 16: America @ Work, 2000; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.6 (2000:June)
  - Item 17: America @ Work, 2000; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.7 (2000:July)
  - Item 18: America @ Work, 2000; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.9 (2000:September)
  - Item 19: America @ Work, 2000; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.10 (2000:October)
  - Item 20: America @ Work, 2000; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.11 (2000:November/December)
- America @ Work 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: America @ Work, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (2001:January)
  - Item 2: America @ Work, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (2001:February)
  - Item 3: America @ Work, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (2001:March)
  - Item 4: America @ Work, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (2001:April)
  - Item 5: America @ Work, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (2001:May)
  - Item 6: America @ Work, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.7 (2001:July)
  - Item 7: America @ Work, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.9 (2001:September)
  - Item 8: America @ Work, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.10 (2001:October)
  - Item 9: America @ Work, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.11 (2001:November/December)
  - Item 10: America @ Work, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (2002:January)
  - Item 11: America @ Work, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (2002:February)
  - Item 12: America @ Work, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (2002:March)
  - Item 13: America @ Work, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (2002:April/May)
  - Item 14: America @ Work, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.5 (2002:June)
  - Item 15: America @ Work, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.6 (2002:July)
  - Item 16: America @ Work, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.8 (2002:September)
  - Item 17: America @ Work, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.9 (2002:October)
  - Item 18: America @ Work, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.10 (2002:November/December)
- America @ Work 2003, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: America @ Work, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (2003:January)
  - Item 2: America @ Work, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (2003:February)
  - Item 3: America @ Work, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: America @ Work, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (2003:March)
  - Item 5: America @ Work, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (2003:April)
  - Item 6: Economy Code Red, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Author: Jane Birnbaum
    Notes: Article from America @ Work, v.8:no.4 (2003:April)
  - Item 7: America @ Work, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.8:no.5 (2003:May)
  - Item 8: America @ Work, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.8:no.6 (2003:June/July)
  - Item 9: America @ Work, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.8:no.6 (2003:June/July). Copy 2.
  - Item 10: America @ Work, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.8:no.7 (2003:August)
  - Item 11: America @ Work, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.8:no.8 (2003:September)
  - Item 12: America @ Work, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.8:no.10 (2003:December)
- America @ Work 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: America @ Work, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.9:no.1 (2004:January/February)
  - Item 2: America @ Work, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.9:no.3 (2004:April)
  - Item 3: America @ Work, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.9:no.5 (2004:June/July)
  - Item 4: America @ Work, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.9:no.7 (2004:September/October)
  - Item 5: America @ Work, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.10:no.1 (2005:January)
  - Item 6: America @ Work, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.10:no.2 (2005:February/March)
- Is There A Place for Unions In the 21st - Century Economy? 2005, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Is There a Place for Unions In the 21st-Century Economy?, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Author: Matt Bai
    Notes: New York Times Magazine, January 30, 2005.
- Calendars 1984-1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: 1996 Calendar, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: District 1199 Rochester and Upstate New York Hospital and Health Care Employees Union, SEIU; Rochester Labor Council
  - Item 2: 1984 Calendar, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: 1199Rochester
- Contract Victory, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: We Did It!, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Author: 1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East
    Notes: Victory Bulletin
  - Item 2: We Won!, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: Nursing Home Contract Victory
  - Item 3: Contract Victory, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Contract Victory, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
- For Your Benefit 2006-2009 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: For Your Benefit Rochester, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Author: 1199SEIU Benefit and Pension Funds
    Notes: March 2006.
  - Item 2: For Your Benefit, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: Summer 2006.
  - Item 3: For Your Benefit, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: Fall 2006/Winter 2007.
  - Item 4: Rochester For Your Benefit, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: Winter 2008-2009.
  - Item 5: For Your Benefit, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: Summer/Fall 2009.